Over the past two years, youth unemployment has been on the rise.
It currently represents just under 40% of all unemployment in Australia.
Young graduates leaving university and finding it more and more difficult to enter any form
of creative industry.
Now the common stipulation is that you can't get a job without experience, but you can't
get a job to get the experience.
Now meanwhile, 42% of small businesses failed in 2003-2007 and the figures haven't improved
much.
Amongst many reasons this is happening is a consistent lack of quality in their branding,
marketing, websites and designs.
The kind of training that these graduates have just spent 3-6 years training for.
Now what if there was an enterprise that bridged these two sets of frightening statistics?
I want to build that bridge.