If we have a one-minute speech to deliver, the main challenge that we face is how do we really
consolidate so much important information into just one minute? And more importantly,
how do we communicate this in a clear manner? That's where this neat little communication
framework called PREC comes into the picture. This framework will not only help us speak in
a concise manner while making sure all the important points are in place, but the best
thing about it is that if we have one-minute speeches or short speeches to give in almost
any occasion, this framework can be applied there. So it also improves our ability to speak on the
spot even when we're not prepared. So what does this framework stand for? PREC. It's
an abbreviation which stands for point, reason, example, point. We basically start off with the
main point or message of our speech. Then we move on to giving a reason for that main point.
Then we give an example and finally end it again with our main point. Let's look at an example.
Let's say we have to give a simple speech around our favorite genre of music. Now,
one of two things can happen. Either we can look at it in a way that there's so much
to speak about under the topic of music, but on the other end, we might also think,
how do I speak beyond just my normal answer? For instance, if our favorite type of music
is jazz, what do we say beyond? Hi, my favorite genre of music is jazz. For both of these instances,
PREC can be very, very useful. Let's get into the example. My favorite type of music
is rock and roll. The reason I like rock and roll music is because I've been listening to
it ever since I was a little kid. And I absolutely love the heavy guitar and the drum
rolls and the lyrics of rock songs. But more than any of this, I remember attending my first
ever rock concert. That atmosphere was electrifying and I remember it to this day.
It immediately made me fall in love with the genre. My favorite rock band is this one group
called Linkin Park. They were one of the first bands that I listened to and I love everything
about them from their melodies to their rhythms to their lyrics. Unfortunately, I never got to
see them perform live, but I still listen to their music every day. And that is why rock
and roll is my favorite type of music. And that's basically it. This framework can be
applied to almost any question or any short speech that we need to give. And if you want
to know more such frameworks that you can apply to short speeches, we've made an entire video
on delivering memorable one-minute speeches, which has a lot more than just frameworks.
And I highly recommend you check that out right here.