Tijana Mihajlović Reviewer's Name
Over the past two years, youth unemployment has been on the rise.
It currently represents just under 40% of all unemployment in Australia.
Young graduates are leaving university
and finding it more and more difficult to enter any form of creative industry.
Now, the common stipulation is that
you can't get a job without experience,
but you can't get a job to get the experience.
Now, meanwhile, 42% of small businesses failed in 2003 to 2007,
and the figures haven't improved much.
Amongst many reasons this is happening
is a consistent lack of quality in their branding, marketing, websites and designs.
The kind of training that these graduates have just spent three to six years training for.
Now, what if there was
an enterprise that bridged these two sets of frightening statistics?
I want to build that bridge.